<?xml version="1.0"?>
<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20190517</CreaDate><CreaTime>16435300</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20220503</ModDate><ModTime>13312800</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><tool name="CreatePercentAccessPolygons" displayname="Create Percent Access Polygons" toolboxalias="TransitNetworkAnalysisTools" xmlns=""><arcToolboxHelpPath>c:\program files\arcgis\pro\Resources\Help\gp</arcToolboxHelpPath><parameters><param name="Input_time_lapse_polygons_feature_class" displayname="Input time lapse polygons feature class" type="Required" direction="Input" datatype="Feature Layer" expression="Input_time_lapse_polygons_feature_class"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;A polygon feature class created using the &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN STYLE="font-style:italic;"&gt;Prepare Time Lapse Polygons&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt; tool that you wish to summarize.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param><param name="Output_percent_access_polygons_feature_class" displayname="Output percent access polygons feature class" type="Required" direction="Output" datatype="Feature Class" expression="Output_percent_access_polygons_feature_class"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The main output feature class of the tool.  This output is a raw raster-like polygon feature class showing the number and percentage of time each area covered by your time lapse polygons was reached, intended primarily for visualization.  The individual polygons are dissolved so that all areas reached the same number of times for a unique combination of FacilityID, FromBreak, and ToBreak are combined into one multipart polygon.  The output feature class must be in a geodatabase; it cannot be a shapefile.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param><param name="cell_size" displayname="Cell size" type="Optional" direction="Input" datatype="Linear Unit" expression="{Meters | Kilometers | Feet | Yards | Miles}"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;This tool rasterizes the input polygons, essentially turning the study area into little squares.  Choose a size for these squares.  The cell size refers to the width or length of the cell, not the area.  Your cell size choice should relate to how pedestrians travel in the real world. You could base your cell size choice on the size of your city blocks or parcels or the distance a pedestrian can walk in less than a minute. Smaller cells are more accurate but take longer to process, and really tiny cells are probably not analytically meaningful.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param><param name="Max_Processes" displayname="Maximum Number of Parallel Processes" type="Required" direction="Input" datatype="Long" expression="Max_Processes"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;For maximum efficiency, this tool performs calculations in parallel across multiple cores of your machine. This parameter designates the number of parallel processes that can safely be used. You should select a number less than or equal to the number of virtual cores or processors your computer has. Note that if you are only processing a single input facility/from break/to break combination, there is nothing to parallelize, so you will get no advantage from increasing the number of processes.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param><param name="Output_threshold_percentage_feature_class" displayname="Output threshold percentage feature class" type="Optional" direction="Output" datatype="Feature Class" expression="{Output_threshold_percentage_feature_class}"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;This is an optional output you can choose to produce that further summarizes the output percent access polygons feature class.  If you specify one or more percentage thresholds, this output contains polygons showing the area reached at least as often as your designated percentage thresholds. There will be a separate feature for each percentage threshold for each unique combination of FacilityID, FromBreak, and ToBreak in the input data.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param><param name="Percentage_thresholds" displayname="Percentage thresholds" type="Optional" direction="Input" datatype="Multiple Value" expression="{Percentage_thresholds;Percentage_thresholds...}"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;You can choose to summarize the tool's raw output for different percentage thresholds.  For example, you can find out what area can be reached at least 75% of start times by setting 75 as one of your percentage thresholds.  More explanation of tool outputs is given below.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param></parameters></tool><dataIdInfo><idCitation><resTitle>Create Percent Access Polygons</resTitle></idCitation></dataIdInfo><distInfo><distributor><distorFormat><formatName>ArcToolbox Tool</formatName></distorFormat></distributor></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"></ScopeCd></mdHrLv><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20220503</mdDateSt></metadata>
